userscripts-mirror.org 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Userscripts.org

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Userscripts.org we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Userscripts.org collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Userscripts.org’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Userscripts.org’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Userscripts.org may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Userscripts.org also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Userscripts.org does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Userscripts.org’s website choose to interact in ways that require Userscripts.org to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Userscripts.org gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. In each case, Userscripts.org collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction. Userscripts.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Userscripts.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Userscripts.org may monitor the most popular scripts. Userscripts.org may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Userscripts.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Userscripts.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Userscripts.org’s behalf or to provide services available at Userscripts.org’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Userscripts.org’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Userscripts.org will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Userscripts.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Userscripts.org believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Userscripts.org, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Userscripts.org website and have supplied your email address, Userscripts.org may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Userscripts.org and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Userscripts.org takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Userscripts.org uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of Userscripts.org website, and their website access preferences. Userscripts.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Userscripts.org website, with the drawback that certain features of Userscripts.org’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Userscripts.org and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Userscripts.org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Userscripts.org’s sole discretion. Userscripts.org encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have an account, you should also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Creative Commons

[](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) Note this privacy policy available under a **Creative Commons Sharealike** license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you. The original policy is by the awesome folks at [Automattic](https://automattic.com/privacy/).
